Lek True NNP False False B-ORG 
Lim True NNP False False I-ORG 
Nonya True NNP False False I-ORG 
Cake True NNP False False I-ORG 
Confectionery True NNP False False I-ORG 
ha False FW False False O 
been False VBN False False O 
working False VBG False False O 
behind False IN False False O 
the False DT False False O 
scene False NN False False O 
supplying False VBG False False O 
hotel False NN False False O 
and False CC False False O 
catering False NN False False O 
companieswith False VBP False False O 
their False PRP$ False False O 
high False JJ False False O 
quality False NN False False O 
handmade False NN False False O 
kuehs False NNS False False O 
. False . False False O 


Roasted True JJ False False B-F 
Duck True NN False False I-F 
with False IN False False I-F 
Hoisin True NN False False I-F 
sauce False NN False False I-F 
4/5 False CD False True S 


At True IN False False O 
Lek True NNP False False B-ORG 
Lim True NNP False False I-ORG 
Nonya True NNP False False I-ORG 
Cake True NNP False False I-ORG 
Confectionery True NNP False False I-ORG 
, False , False False O 
both False CC False False O 
the False DT False False O 
Steamed True JJ False False B-F 
Yam True NN False False I-F 
Cake True FW False False I-F 
( False FW False False O 
$ False $ False False B-P 
0.80/pc False FW False False I-P 
) False FW False False O 
and False CC False False O 
Fried True NNP False False B-F 
Yam True NNP False False I-F 
Cake True NNP False False I-F 
( False NNP False False O 
$ False $ False False B-P 
0.80/pc False CD False False I-P 
) False CD False False O 
come False VBN False False O 
with False IN False False O 
delectable False JJ False False O 
chunky False JJ False False O 
yam False NN False False O 
bite False NN False False O 
, False , False False O 
fragrant False JJ False False O 
mushroom False NN False False O 
and False CC False False O 
dried False VBD False False O 
shrimp False NN False False O 
. False . False False O 


At True IN False False O 
Lek True NNP False False B-ORG 
Lim True NNP False False I-ORG 
Nonya True NNP False False I-ORG 
Cake True NNP False False I-ORG 
Confectionery True NNP False False I-ORG 
, False , False False O 
both False CC False False O 
the False DT False False O 
Steamed True JJ False False B-F 
Yam True NN False False I-F 
Cake True FW False False I-F 
( False FW False False O 
$ False $ False False B-P 
0.80/pc False FW False False I-P 
) False FW False False O 
and False CC False False O 
Fried True NNP False False B-F 
Yam True NNP False False I-F 
Cake True NNP False False I-F 
( False NNP False False O 
$ False $ False False B-P 
0.80/pc False CD False False I-P 
) False CD False False O 
come False VBN False False O 
with False IN False False O 
delectable False JJ False False O 
chunky False JJ False False O 
yam False NN False False O 
bite False NN False False O 
, False , False False O 
fragrant False JJ False False O 
mushroom False NN False False O 
and False CC False False O 
dried False VBD False False O 
shrimp False NN False False O 
. False . False False O 


Festive True JJ False False O 
Celebrations True NNS False False O 
at False IN False False O 
The True DT False False O 
Square True NNP False False O 
RestaurantDate True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
10 False CD True False O 
December True NNP False False O 
2012 False CD True False O 
to False TO False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
January True NNP False False O 
2013 False CD True False O 
Festive True NNP False False I-ORG 
Lunch True NNP False False I-ORG 
Buffet True NNP False False I-ORG 
: False : False False O 
Mon-Fri True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
12pm False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
230pm False NN False False O 
10 False CD True False O 
Dec True NNP False False O 
2012 False CD True False O 
- False : False False O 
31 False CD True False O 
Dec True NNP False False O 
2012 False CD True False O 
: False : False False O 
Adult True JJ False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
42++ False CD False False O 
Child True NNP False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
25++ False CD False False O 
Senior True NNP False False O 
Citizens True NNPS False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
30++ False CD False False O 
Festive True JJ False False B-F 
Dinner True NN False False I-F 
Buffet True NN False False I-F 
: False : False False O 
Mon-Sun True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
6pm False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
10pm False CD False False O 
10 False CD True False O 
Dec True NNP False False O 
12 False CD True False O 
- False : False False O 
01 False CD True False O 
Jan True NNP False False O 
13 False CD True False O 
( False NNP False False O 
Sun-Thu True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Adult True JJ False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
52++ False CD False False O 
Child True NNP False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
35++ False CD False False O 
Senior True NNP False False O 
Citizens True NNPS False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
35++ False CD False False O 
10 False CD True False O 
Dec True NNP False False O 
12 False CD True False O 
- False : False False O 
01 False CD True False O 
Jan True NNP False False O 
13 False CD True False O 
( False NNP False False O 
Fri-Sat True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Adult True JJ False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
62++ False CD False False O 
Child True NNP False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
38++ False CD False False O 
Senior True NNP False False O 
Citizens True NNPS False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
38++ False CD False False O 
Festive True JJ False False O 
Brunch True NNP False False O 
Buffet True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Sat-Sun True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1130am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
3pm False NN False False O 
15 False CD True False O 
Dec True NNP False False O 
12 False CD True False O 
- False : False False O 
30 False CD True False O 
Dec True NNP False False O 
12 False CD True False O 
, False , False False O 
25 False CD True False O 
Dec True NNP False False O 
12 False CD True False O 
& False CC False False O 
01 False CD True False O 
Jan True NNP False False O 
13 False CD True False O 
: False : False False O 
Adult True JJ False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
68++ False CD False False O 
Child True NNP False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
48++ False CD False False O 
Senior True NNP False False O 
Citizens True NNPS False False O 
$ False $ False False O 
48++ False CD False False O 
( False CD False False O 
buffet False NN False False O 
only False RB False False O 
) False CD False False O 
. False . False False O 


MOUTH True NNP False False B-ORG 
RESTAURANT True NNP False False I-ORG 
Mouth True NNP False False B-ORG 
Restaurant True NNP False False I-ORG 
( False NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
China True NNP False False B-LOC 
Square True NNP False False I-LOC 
Central True NNP False False I-LOC 
South True NNP False False I-LOC 
Bridge True NNP False False I-LOC 
Court True NNP False False I-LOC 
Shop True NNP False False I-LOC 
House True NNP False False I-LOC 
22 False CD True False I-LOC 
Cross True NNP False False I-LOC 
Street True NNP False False I-LOC 
# False # False False I-LOC 
01-61 False CD False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
048421 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
64385798 False CD True False I-HP 
Facebook True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.facebook.com/pages/Mouth-Restaurant- False NN False False O 
% False NN False False O 
E5 True CD False False O 
% False NN False False O 
9C False CD False False O 
% False NN False False O 
B0 True NN False False O 
% False NN False False O 
E8 True CD False False O 
% False NN False False O 
8C False CD False False O 
% False NN False False O 
82 False CD True False O 
% False NN False False O 
E9 True CD False False O 
% False NN False False O 
A6 True NN False False O 
% False NN False False O 
86/213508241996944 False CD False True O 
Website True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.mouth.com.sg False NNP False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Chinatown True FW False False O 
( False FW False False O 
NE True NN False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Weekday True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1130am False FW False False O 
-3pm False FW False False O 
, False , False False O 
6pm False JJ False False O 
- False : False False O 
10pm False JJ False False O 
Weekend True NNP False False O 
& False CC False False O 
PH True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
10am False CD False False O 
- False : False False O 
10pm False JJ False False O 
Direction True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Chinatown True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
. False . False False O 


RAMEN True NNP False False B-ORG 
KEISUKE True NNP False False I-ORG 
TORI True NNP False False I-ORG 
KING True NNP False False I-ORG 
Ramen True NNP False False B-ORG 
Kaisuke True NNP False False I-ORG 
Tori True NNP False False I-ORG 
King True NNP False False I-ORG 
Amara True NNP False False B-LOC 
Hotel True NNP False False I-LOC 
Shopping True NNP False False I-LOC 
Mall True NN False False I-LOC 
100AM False CD False False I-LOC 
100 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tras True NNP False False I-LOC 
Street True NNP False False I-LOC 
# False # False False I-LOC 
03-15 False CD False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
088539 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
66046861 False CD True False I-HP 
Facebook True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.facebook.com/KeisukeTokyoSG False NN False False O 
Website True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.grandcuisine.jp/keisuke/ False NNP False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Tanjong True NNP False False O 
Pagar True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
EW True NNP False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Daily True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1130am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
3pm False NN False False O 
, False , False False O 
530pm False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
10pm False JJ False False O 
Direction True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
) False CD False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Tanjong True NNP False False O 
Pagar True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
. False . False False O 


Majestic True NNP False False B-ORG 
Bay True NNP False False I-ORG 
Seafood True NNP False False I-ORG 
Restaurant True NNP False False I-ORG 
Gardens True NNP False False B-LOC 
by False IN False False I-LOC 
the False DT False False I-LOC 
Bay True NNP False False I-LOC 
Flower True NNP False False I-LOC 
Dome True NNP False False I-LOC 
18 False CD True False I-LOC 
Marina True NNP False False I-LOC 
Gardens True NNP False False I-LOC 
Drive True NNP False False I-LOC 
# False # False False I-LOC 
01-10 False CD False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
018953 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
66046604 False CD True False I-HP 
Facebook True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.facebook.com/MajesticBay False NN False False O 
Website True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.majesticbay.sg False NNP False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Bayfront True FW False False O 
( False FW False False O 
CC True NN False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
, False , False False O 
Marina True NNP False False O 
Bay True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
CC True NN False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
, False , False False O 
NS True NNP False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Mon-Fri True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1145am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
230pm False NN False False O 
, False , False False O 
545pm False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
930pm False FW False False O 
( False FW False False O 
last False JJ False False O 
order False NN False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Sat True NNP False False O 
, False , False False O 
Sun True NNP False False O 
& False CC False False O 
PH True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1130am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
230pm False NN False False O 
, False , False False O 
545pm False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
930pm False FW False False O 
( False FW False False O 
last False JJ False False O 
order False NN False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Direction True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
) False CD False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Marina True NNP False False O 
Bay True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
. False . False False O 


Caffe True NNP False False B-ORG 
B True NNP False False I-ORG 
The True NNP False False B-LOC 
Shoppes True NNPS False False I-LOC 
@ False SYM False False I-LOC 
Marina True NNP False False I-LOC 
Bay True NNP False False I-LOC 
Sands True NNP False False I-LOC 
2 False CD True False I-LOC 
Bayfront True NNP False False I-LOC 
Avenue True NNP False False I-LOC 
# False # False False I-LOC 
B1-15 True NNP False False I-LOC 
& False CC False False I-LOC 
01-83 False NNP False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
018972 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
68873311 False CD True False I-HP 
Facebook True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.facebook.com/caffeb.singapore False NN False False O 
Website True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.caffeb.com.sg False NNP False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Bayfront True FW False False O 
( False FW False False O 
CC True NN False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Restaurant True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Daily True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
12pm False JJ False False O 
- False : False False O 
3pm False JJ False False O 
, False , False False O 
6pm False JJ False False O 
- False : False False O 
11pm False JJ False False O 
Bar True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
Sun-Wed True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
11am False CD False False O 
- False : False False O 
11pm False FW False False O 
Thu-Sat True FW False False O 
& False CC False False O 
even False RB False False O 
of False IN False False O 
PH True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
11am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
till False IN False False O 
late False JJ False False O 
Direction True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
) False CD False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Bayfront True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
Exit True NN False False O 
and False CC False False O 
walk False NN False False O 
towards False IN False False O 
The True DT False False O 
Shoppes True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Marina True NNP False False O 
Bay True NNP False False O 
Sands True NNP False False O 
. False . False False O 



Ruths True NNP False False B-ORG 
Chris True NNP False False I-ORG 
Steak True NNP False False I-ORG 
House True NNP False False I-ORG 
Marina True NNP False False B-LOC 
Mandarin True NNP False False I-LOC 
Hotel True NNP False False I-LOC 
6 False CD True False I-LOC 
Raffles True NNP False False I-LOC 
Boulevard True NNP False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
039594 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
63369093 False CD True False I-HP 
Website True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.ruthschris.com/ False NNP False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Esplanade True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
CC True NN False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Daily True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1130am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
3pm False NN False False O 
, False , False False O 
530pm False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
11pm False JJ False False O 
Direction True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
) False CD False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Esplanade True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
. False . False False O 


Albert True NNP False False B-ORG 
Street True NNP False False I-ORG 
Prawn True NNP False False I-ORG 
Noodle True NNP False False I-ORG 
Lavendar True NNP False False I-ORG 
Food True NNP False False B-LOC 
Square True NNP False False I-LOC 
380 False CD True False I-LOC 
Jalan True NNP False False I-LOC 
Besar True NNP False False I-LOC 
# False # False False I-LOC 
01-10 False CD False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
209000 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
62951340 False CD True False I-HP 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Lavender True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
EW True NNP False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
, False , False False O 
Boon True NNP False False O 
Keng True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
NE True NN False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Daily True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
10am False CD False False O 
- False : False False O 
3am False FW False False O 
( False FW False False O 
Closed True JJ False False O 
on False IN False False O 
alt False NN False False O 
Thursday True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Direction True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
) False CD False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Lavender True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
. False . False False O 


Japanese True NNP False False B-ORG 
Dining True NNP False False I-ORG 
SUN True NNP False False I-ORG 
Chijmes True NNP False False I-ORG 
30 False CD True False B-LOC 
Victoria True NNP False False I-LOC 
Street True NNP False False I-LOC 
# False # False False I-LOC 
02-01 False CD False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
187996 False NNP True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
63363166 False CD True False I-HP 
Facebook True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.facebook.com/pages/Japanese-Dining-SUN-Chijmes/112908922053939 False NN False False O 
Website True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.sundining.com.sg/sun-dining-chijmes.html False NN False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
City True NNP False False O 
Hall True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
EW True NNP False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
, False , False False O 
NS True NNP False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
, False , False False O 
Bras True NNP False False O 
Basah True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
CC True NN False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Lunch True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
Sun-Fri True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
12pm False CD False False O 
- False : False False O 
3pm False FW False False O 
Dinner True FW False False O 
( False FW False False O 
Mon-Sat True FW False False O 
) False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
630pm False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
11pm False JJ False False O 
Sun True NNP False False O 
& False CC False False O 
PH True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
6pm False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
1030pm False JJ False False O 
Direction True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
) False CD False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
City True NNP False False O 
Hall True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
. False . False False O 


Caffe True NNP False False B-ORG 
B True NNP False False I-ORG 
The True NNP False False B-LOC 
Shoppes True NNPS False False I-LOC 
@ False SYM False False I-LOC 
Marina True NNP False False I-LOC 
Bay True NNP False False I-LOC 
Sands True NNP False False I-LOC 
2 False CD True False I-LOC 
Bayfront True NNP False False I-LOC 
Avenue True NNP False False I-LOC 
# False # False False I-LOC 
B1-15 True NNP False False I-LOC 
& False CC False False I-LOC 
01-83 False NNP False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
018972 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
68873311 False CD True False I-HP 
Facebook True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.facebook.com/caffeb.singapore False NN False False O 
Website True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.caffeb.com.sg False NNP False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Bayfront True FW False False O 
( False FW False False O 
CC True NN False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Restaurant True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Daily True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
12pm False JJ False False O 
- False : False False O 
3pm False JJ False False O 
, False , False False O 
6pm False JJ False False O 
- False : False False O 
11pm False JJ False False O 
Bar True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
Sun-Wed True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
11am False CD False False O 
- False : False False O 
11pm False FW False False O 
Thu-Sat True FW False False O 
& False CC False False O 
even False RB False False O 
of False IN False False O 
PH True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
11am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
till False IN False False O 
late False JJ False False O 
Direction True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
) False CD False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Bayfront True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
Exit True NN False False O 
and False CC False False O 
walk False NN False False O 
towards False IN False False O 
The True DT False False O 
Shoppes True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Marina True NNP False False O 
Bay True NNP False False O 
Sands True NNP False False O 
. False . False False O 


Stellar True JJ False False B-ORG 
@ False SYM False False I-ORG 
1 False CD True False I-ORG 
Altitude True NN False False I-ORG 
One True CD False False B-LOC 
Raffles True NN False False I-LOC 
Place True NN False False I-LOC 
1 False CD True False I-LOC 
Raffles True NNP False False I-LOC 
Place True NNP False False I-LOC 
Level True NNP False False I-LOC 
62 False CD True False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
048616 False CD True False I-LOC 
Website True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.1-altitude.com/ False JJ False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Raffles True NNP False False O 
Place True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
NS True NNP False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
, False , False False O 
EW True NNP False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Mon-Fri True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1130am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
230pm False NN False False O 
, False , False False O 
6pm False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
12am False FW False False O 
Sat True FW False False O 
, False , False False O 
Sun True NNP False False O 
& False CC False False O 
PH True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
6pm False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
12am False JJ False False O 
Direction True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Raffles True NNP False False O 
Place True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
. False . False False O 


Double True JJ False False O 
Shot True NN False False O 
Instant True JJ False False O 
WhiteMilk True FW False False O 
Tea+ True FW False False O 
Hello True UH False False O 
Kitty True NNP False False O 
Cup True NNP False False O 


Caffe True NNP False False B-ORG 
B True NNP False False I-ORG 
The True NNP False False B-LOC 
Shoppes True NNPS False False I-LOC 
@ False SYM False False I-LOC 
Marina True NNP False False I-LOC 
Bay True NNP False False I-LOC 
Sands True NNP False False I-LOC 
2 False CD True False I-LOC 
Bayfront True NNP False False I-LOC 
Avenue True NNP False False I-LOC 
# False # False False I-LOC 
B1-15 True NNP False False I-LOC 
& False CC False False I-LOC 
01-83 False NNP False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
018972 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
68873311 False CD True False I-HP 
Facebook True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.facebook.com/caffeb.singapore False NN False False O 
Website True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.caffeb.com.sg False NNP False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Bayfront True FW False False O 
( False FW False False O 
CC True NN False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Restaurant True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Daily True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
12pm False JJ False False O 
- False : False False O 
3pm False JJ False False O 
, False , False False O 
6pm False JJ False False O 
- False : False False O 
11pm False JJ False False O 
Bar True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
Sun-Wed True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
11am False CD False False O 
- False : False False O 
11pm False FW False False O 
Thu-Sat True FW False False O 
& False CC False False O 
even False RB False False O 
of False IN False False O 
PH True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
11am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
till False IN False False O 
late False JJ False False O 
Direction True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
) False CD False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Bayfront True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
Exit True NN False False O 
and False CC False False O 
walk False NN False False O 
towards False IN False False O 
The True DT False False O 
Shoppes True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Marina True NNP False False O 
Bay True NNP False False O 
Sands True NNP False False O 
. False . False False O 


Sushi True NNP False False B-ORG 
Tei True NNP False False I-ORG 
Takashimaya True NNP False False B-LOC 
Ngee True NNP False False I-LOC 
Ann True NNP False False I-LOC 
City True NNP False False I-LOC 
Podium True NNP False False I-LOC 
Block True NNP False False I-LOC 
391 False CD True False I-LOC 
Orchard True NNP False False I-LOC 
Road True NNP False False I-LOC 
# False # False False I-LOC 
05-30/31 False CD False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
238872 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
67378878 False CD True False I-HP 
Website True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.sushitei.com/ False NNP False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Orchard True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
NS True NNP False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
, False , False False O 
Somerset True NNP False False O 
( False NNP False False O 
NS True NNP False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Daily True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1130am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
10pm False JJ False False O 
Direction True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
) False CD False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Orchard True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
. False . False False O 


CAFFE True NN False False B-ORG 
B True NN False False I-ORG 
Caffe True NN False False I-ORG 
B True NN False False I-ORG 
The True DT False False B-LOC 
Shoppes True NNPS False False I-LOC 
@ False SYM False False I-LOC 
Marina True NNP False False I-LOC 
Bay True NNP False False I-LOC 
Sands True NNP False False I-LOC 
2 False CD True False I-LOC 
Bayfront True NNP False False I-LOC 
Avenue True NNP False False I-LOC 
# False # False False I-LOC 
B1-15 True NNP False False I-LOC 
& False CC False False I-LOC 
01-83 False NNP False False I-LOC 
Singapore True NNP False False I-LOC 
018972 False CD True False I-LOC 
Tel True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
+65 False CD False False B-HP 
68873311 False CD True False I-HP 
Facebook True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.facebook.com/caffeb.singapore False NN False False O 
Website True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
http False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
//www.caffeb.com.sg False NNP False False O 
Nearest True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Bayfront True FW False False O 
( False FW False False O 
CC True NN False False O 
Line True NNP False False O 
) False NNP False False O 
Opening True NNP False False O 
Hours True NNS False False O 
: False : False False O 
Restaurant True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
Daily True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
12pm False JJ False False O 
- False : False False O 
3pm False JJ False False O 
, False , False False O 
6pm False JJ False False O 
- False : False False O 
11pm False JJ False False O 
Bar True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
Sun-Wed True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
11am False CD False False O 
- False : False False O 
11pm False FW False False O 
Thu-Sat True FW False False O 
& False CC False False O 
even False RB False False O 
of False IN False False O 
PH True NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
11am False NN False False O 
- False : False False O 
till False IN False False O 
late False JJ False False O 
Direction True NNP False False O 
: False : False False O 
1 False CD True False O 
) False CD False False O 
Alight True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Bayfront True NNP False False O 
MRT True NNP False False O 
station False NN False False O 
: False : False False O 
Exit True NN False False O 
and False CC False False O 
walk False NN False False O 
towards False IN False False O 
The True DT False False O 
Shoppes True NNP False False O 
at False IN False False O 
Marina True NNP False False O 
Bay True NNP False False O 
Sands True NNP False False O 
. False . False False O 

